（澳洲 悉尼）
（拜塞制药厂）
狄米特 每个英雄的诞生
Well, Dmitri, every search for a hero…
都有一个必备的条件
must begin with something that every hero requires…
有坏蛋出现
a villain.
为了寻求我们的英雄…伯洛尔芬
Therefore, in the search for our hero, Bellerophon,
我们制造了一头恶魔
we created a monster,
奇美拉
Chimera.
狄米特 我求你立刻来悉尼
I beg you, Dmitri, come to Sydney…
陪我去亚特兰大
and accompany me to Atlanta immediately.
无论如何 出发后二十小时内
However we travel, I must arrive at my destination…
必须抵达目的地
within 20 hours of departure.
各位 两个半小时后就抵达亚特兰大
Folks, we're two-and-a-half hours from Atlanta.
窗外是壮观的落基山脉
Look out your window now. We have a great view of the Rocky Mountains.
你不断看表 彷佛生死攸关
You keep staring at that watch as if your life depended on it, Doctor.
是的
Oh, yes.
我是有点紧张
I suppose I'm a bit anxious.
你很快就见到老朋友了
You'll soon be with old friends.
你也是老朋友 狄米特
I'm with an old friend now, Dmitri.
很抱歉是这种情况下见面
I'm sorry it couldn't be under happier circumstances.
我也很抱歉
I'm sorry too.
你很抱歉 我也很抱歉
You are sorry, and I am sorry.
葛斯基很欣赏你
You don't know Gradski thought the world of you.
他在死前…
Did he…know…
知不知道你们研制成功？
before the end that you two had succeeded?
是的 他知道 只是…
Yes, he knew. Just…
来不及救他
Not in time to save him.
没错
No.
感染上奇美拉病毒超过二十小时…什么都救不了你
After you've been infected with Chimera for 20 hours, nothing can save you.
连伯洛尔芬抗毒素都没用
Not even Bellerophon.
病毒和抗毒素放在一起 安全吗？
You can carry them together…safely?
安全
Yes.
可到了亚特兰大 你还得给我们找个安全的地方
And you'll get us to safe place with them in Atlanta, thank God.
我是机长 机舱的气压…
This is your captain again. We've experienced a slight…
突然减低
but abrupt drop in cabin pressure.
为了安全起见 我放下氧气罩
As a precaution, I've released the oxygen masks.
请各位戴上坐稳 放松
Please put them on and sit back, relax.
无须恐慌
There's nothing to worry about.
你担不担心？
Are you concerned?
暂时不担心
Not so far.
你戴上氧气罩 我去看看
Just put on your oxygen mask. I'll see what's going on.
好
Okay.
丹佛中心 这是泛太平洋2207号747客机
Denver Center, this is Trans-Pac 2207, 747 heavy.
我们没法维持机舱气压
We're unable to maintain cabin pressurization.
我们准备下降到一万六千英尺
We've initiated a descent to one six thousand.
机长…
Captain…
狄米特 我们似乎有麻烦
It seems we have a problem, Dmitri.
不要总叫我狄米特 不应该这样叫
You keep calling me Dmitri. You really shouldn't.
你不是狄米特？
You are not Dmitri?
我不是
No.
华莱士 拿着
Wallis, hold on to this.
欧利 记得…
Ulrich, remember to pull the…
记得把毒气筒丢掉
Remember to pull the NO2 tank and dump it.
知道了 老大
All done, chief.
前面有山脉 升高…
Terrain. Terrain. Pull up. Pull up.
到达跳伞点！倒数三
Okay, dive, dive! Checkpoint Charlie in three,
二 一 跳！
two, one, go!
前面有山脉 升高…
Terrain. Terrain. Pull up. Pull up.
早晨好 亨特先生
Good morning, Mr. Hunt.
如果你接受这项任务
Your mission, should you choose to accept it,
必须负责取回失窃物奇美拉
involves the recovery of a stolen item designated "Chimera".
你可以挑选任何两名队员
You may select any two team members,
不过第三名必须是娜雅·霍尔
but it is essential that the third team member be Nyah Nordoff-Hall.
她是一名身手不凡的女窃贼
She is a civilian and a highly capable professional thief.
你要48小时内招揽到霍小姐
You have 48 hours to recruit Miss Nordoff-Hall…
然后到塞维利亚见我 接受任务
and meet me in Seville to receive your assignment.
一如既往 假如你们被捕或殉职
As always, should you or any member of your IMF team be caught or killed,
政府将完全否认涉及此事
the secretary will disavow all knowledge of your actions.
亨特先生 下次去度假
And, Mr. Hunt, the next time you go on holiday,
请让我们知道你去哪里
please be good enough to let us know where you're going.
本讯息五秒后自动毁灭
This message will self-destruct in five seconds.
如果你知道我去哪里
If I let you know where I'm going…
我不会有假放
then I won't be on holiday.
《碟中谍2》
（西班牙 塞维利亚）
你找到了
I see you found it.
你在这儿干嘛？
What are you doing here?
你以为只有你会开锁吗？
Think you're the only one who can pick a lock?
原来你不只是脸蛋漂亮
Huh. You're not just a pretty face after all.
不介意我在上面吧？
Do you mind if I'm on top?
不会 两种姿势我都喜欢
No. Either way works for me.
- 你找不到的 - 该死
- You'll never find it there. - Damn it!
你知道我想找什么？
Find what?
他的宝格丽项链于星期二拍卖
His ex's Bulgari necklace that goes up for auction on Tuesday.
你要告诉我在哪儿？
And are you gonna tell me where it is?
最左面
Far left.
你让我分心
This is very disconcerting.
是你要我在下面 我很听话
Hey, you put me here. I just do as I'm told.
好吧
Right.
那么 你是谁？
Now, who are you…
我得付出什么？
and what's it gonna cost me?
- 你最好别那样 - 不要什么？
- I wouldn't do that. - What?
关上
That.
不用紧张
No, no, no. Tranquilo. Tranquilo.
齐先生 原来是你
Mr. Keys, it is you.
我们的保安主任齐先生 快道歉
It is Mr. Keys, our security engineer. Apologize!
不用道歉…
No, no. No need to apologize.
我同事霍小姐把项链藏好了
Now, Miss Hall, my associate has your necklace in a very safe place.
但是警铃应该早一点响
But obviously we do feel the alarm should have gone off a little sooner.
- 对吗？霍小姐 - 对极
- Isn't that right, Miss Hall? - Hmm? Oh, absolutely.
响得太迟了
Much, much too long, I'd say.
因此 我建议…
Under the circumstances, I think we'd recommend…
要调整感应器的承重度
resetting the sensors to respond to a lighter load.
霍小姐 四十公斤如何？
How do you feel about 40 kilos, Miss Hall?
好极
Perfect.
我们走吗？
Shall we?
- 霍小姐 - 恩？
- Miss Hall. - Hmm?
你有没有忘记什么？
Haven't you forgotten something?
小姐 你打算顺手牵羊？
What are you trying to do, señorita? Rob me?
我是有想过
The thought had crossed my mind.
五十万镑的项链 得而复失
I'm missing something here, aside from my half-million-pound necklace.
我就算搞砸了
Even after I screwed up the job,
还是能把它带走
I could've walked out of there with the bloody thing.
你能走就很好了
At least you walked.
为什么袖手旁观 不逮捕我？
Why did you watch me go through it all?
我想看你有多高明 我希望跟你合作
I wanted to see how good you were. I was hoping we might work together.
听起来很棒 小子
Sounds terrific. Muchacho.
言归正传 身手已见识过
Now be serious. Whatever you're talking about,
该打消念头吧
you couldn't possibly want me after tonight's performance.
- 你身手并不太差 - 替我打圆场？
- You didn't do that badly. - You apologizing for me?
真有绅士风度…谢谢
Quite the gentleman. Gracias.
不见得 警铃是我启动的
Not really. I triggered the alarm.
对不起
Sorry.
我讨厌做家务 更讨厌那些…
I don't do laundry, cook, or put up with cheeky bastards
故意整我的混蛋
who set me up on their territory so they can poach on mine.
小姐 开慢一点好不好？
Hi. Would you mind slowing down?
你怎么知道号码？我都不知道
Where did you get this number? I don't even have it.
你想知道吗？
Would you like it?
靠边停车听我说 听我说
Pull over and listen to me, will you? Just listen.
- 听你说什么？- 我要你帮忙
- Listen to what? - I need your help.
- 你或者也需要我帮忙 - 你帮我？
- And I think you could use mine. - Your help?
- 帮我什么？- 我可以让苏格兰警场
- What are you talking about? - I'm talking about Scotland Yard,
国际刑警 荷兰警方
Interpol, every Dutch authority.
- 都对你既往不咎 - 靠
- I can make them all go away. - Oh, bloody hell.
原来你是间谍 你想我合作
You're a spy! Well, if you want me,
抓到再说
you've gotta catch me!
你想玩？
You having fun?
抱歉
Sorry.
白痴！
Idiota.
抱歉
Sorry.
看路…
Watch the road. Watch the road.
你叫什么名字？
What's your name?
伊森·亨特
Ethan Hunt.
Well, Ethan Hunt,
你找我做什么？
what is it you want to talk to me about?
我想做的不言而喻
A lot more than I thought.
未免太快了
Awfully short notice.
你要我慢慢来吗？
Care to wait a decent interval?
谁想要慢慢来？
Who wants to be decent?
为什么讨厌间谍？
So what have you got against spies?
他们用你这种方式招聘间谍？
When they've got your recruiting technique?
我没有照规矩来
This wasn't exactly by the book.
这种事也有规矩吗？
They've got a book for this?
什么都有规矩
Oh, they've got a book for everything.
那么 所失窃的东西…
So, this thing these blokes pinched…
我不知道是不是失窃
I don't know that they pinched it.
也不确定他们是贼
I don't even know that they're blokes.
那么你要我干什么？
What am I doing here?
还以为你要我…
And I thought I'm supposed to be…
以贼捉贼
some kind of thief to catch a thief.
我也以为…大约如此
So do I…sort of.
你真漂亮
Damn, you're beautiful.
义式咖啡？卡布其诺？
Espresso? Cappuccino?
- 不用客气 - 请坐
- No, thanks. - Sit down. Sit down.
节庆真烦人 他们用焚烧圣像来纪念圣人
Festival's a pain in the ass. Honoring their saints by setting them on fire.
这算哪门子的尊敬？
Lets you know what they think of saints, doesn't it?
刚才我差点也被烧到
Damn near set me on fire on my way over here.
抱歉中断了你的假期
Sorry I barged in on your vacation.
抱歉我没说我在哪儿
I'm sorry I didn't let you know where I was.
别道歉 说了就不算度假
Don't be. It wouldn't be a vacation if you did.
你很抱歉 我也很抱歉
You're sorry, and I'm sorry.
你为什么这么说？
Why did you phrase it like that?
- 怎么说？ - 你抱歉 我也抱歉
- Like what? - "You're sorry; I'm sorry."
你在耍我吗？
You've gotta be kidding.
狄米特 我又要你帮忙了
Well, Dmitri, once again I need your help.
就像以前一样
Just as in the old days, huh?
你救了我们的性命和灵魂
When you saved our lives, saved our very sanity.
狄米特…
Dmitri…
我们有…小小一个问题
we have this little problem.
每个英雄的诞生
Every search for a hero…
都有一个必备的条件
must begin with something that every hero requires…
一个坏蛋
a villain.
为了寻求我们的英雄伯洛尔芬
Therefore, in the search for our hero, Bellerophon,
我们制造了一头恶魔…奇美拉
we created a monster, Chimera.
狄米特 我求你
I beg you, Dmitri,
立即来悉尼 陪我去亚特兰大
come to Sydney and accompany me to Atlanta immediately.
无论如何…出发后二十小时内…
However we travel, I must arrive at my destination…
必须抵达目的地
within 20 hours of departure.
现在…我只有你一个信得过
I fear I can entrust this to no one but you.
狄米特 我们说过 我很抱歉 你也很抱歉
Dmitri, as we say, I'm sorry and you're sorry.
他说的这些你是怎么想的？
Do you have any idea what the hell he's talking about?
- 有点头绪 - 怎样？
- An idea? Yeah. - Like?
我们应该尽快去接他
Like it's a good idea to pick him up in a hurry…
而且用专机去接
and a bad idea to fly him on a commercial carrier.
- 他在悉尼？- 诺考维奇博士已经死了
- Is he still in Sydney? - Dr. Vladimir Nekhovich is dead.
他的同事葛斯基较早前也死了
So is his colleague Gradski, but that happened earlier.
诺考维奇的飞机 在落基山脉撞毁
We had Nekhovich on a flight from Sydney that crashed in the Rockies.
- 死了…- 你在听着吗？
- Dead? - Are you listening to me?
假如他一定要有我陪才走…
If he didn't want to go anywhere without me,
他怎么肯搭飞机？
how did you get him on that flight?
因为你去了
Oh, you were there.
我找不到你 只好找别人代替你
When I couldn't find you, I had to replace you.
西恩·安柏斯是最佳人选
Sean Ambrose was the obvious choice.
他扮过你两三次了吧？
Now, he doubled you, what, two or three times?
- 两次 - 你认为他怎样？
- Twice. - What did you think of him?
我们不太合得来
We had our reservations about each other.
现在问未免太迟了
Isn't it a little late to be asking me that?
未必 根据航空公司的记录…
No, not necessarily. Airline records…
2207班机的机长叫麦哈洛
list a Captain Harold Macintosh as the pilot of flight 2207.
媒体和政府都认为
As far as the media and all government agencies are concerned,
麦哈洛机长死于空难
Captain Macintosh died on the flight.
但是他没搭那班机
But, in fact, he missed it.
他搭下一班机的货舱
He did, however, make the next flight…in cargo.
他是个大汉 却挤在小行李箱里
Stuffed into a rather small suitcase, considering his size.
即是说 有人在飞机上动了手脚
Now, someone on that flight planned an operation…
暗中把飞机坠毁 造成意外的假象
designed to bring the plane down and make it look like an accident.
而且没留下蛛丝马迹
Someone skillful enough to bring the whole thing off without a hitch.
这个人必定是安柏斯
So there's one thing we know that Ambrose doesn't.
你为什么认定是他？你不惊讶？
You do think it was Ambrose? You're not surprised?
他每次出动 不杀人不甘心
Sean feels he hasn't done the job unless he leaves a lot of hats on the ground.
问题是为什么？诺考维奇 所携带的奇美拉是什么？
The question is why? What was this, uh, Chimera, Nekhovich was carrying?
只有安柏斯才知道
Only Ambrose knows that.
无论如何 你要找奇美拉…并且带它回来
In any case, you must recover this…whatever…Chimera, and bring it to us.
我想知他如何用奇美拉来赚钱
In order to do that, I have to figure out how he plans to make money with it.
所以要出动霍小姐
That is where Miss Hall comes in.
什么？
Excuse me?
霍小姐和他本来是情人
Miss Hall and Ambrose had a relationship which he took very seriously.
她走掉 安一直望她回心转意
She walked away, and he's been wanting her back ever since.
霍小姐出马 十拿九稳找到他
We believe she's our surest and quickest way of locating him.
然后呢？
And then what?
让她继续跟他交往
Well, make sure she continues to see him,
套出他的话再向你报告
gets him to confide in her, and report to you.
你当初叫我招揽她 好像是为了她的偷窃才能
You made it sound as if I was recruiting her for her skills as a thief.
或者我误导了你 或者你会错意
Well, then I misled you, or you made the wrong assumption.
我们只是请她继续一段恋情
Either way, we're asking her to resume a prior relationship,
并不是勉强她做什么
not do anything she hasn't already done.
当然是出于自愿
Voluntarily, I might add.
不行 她没有受过这种训练
No, she's got no training for this kind of thing.
她只要跟男人上床 她是女人
What, to go to bed with a man and lie to him? She's a woman.
这是她与生俱来的天赋
She's got all the training she needs.
我想我说服不了她
I don't think I can get her to do it.
- 你认为困难？- 非常困难
- You mean it'll be difficult. - Very.
这不是困难的任务 这是不可能的任务
Well, this is not Mission Difficult, Mr. Hunt, it's Mission Impossible.
困难对于你就像公园散步一样简单
Difficult should be a walk in the park for you.
给你个建议
I'm open to suggestion.
要是你有办法对付安柏斯 尽管去试
If you can think of a quicker way, you're welcome to try.
觉得对她良心不安的话…
You might take a look at these…
不妨看看这些照片
if you have any further qualms about getting her to do the job.
谁会这样狠心 滥杀无辜？
How many people are capable of something like that?
西恩·安柏斯
Sean Ambrose, for one.
对
Right.
我当初没打算要你这样做
This wasn't what I had in mind, Nyah.
但你现在希望我自愿做
But it is what you'd like me to do.
怎样？你以为我有正义感肯接受任务？
What? Oh, let my conscience be my guide, is that it?
大概是
Something like that.
我没有正义感 我只是个贼！
I don't have a conscience. I'm a bloody thief.
你要逼我去做吗？
Are you gonna try and force me to do this?
一般来说 我不会逼任何人
Generally, I don't favor coercing someone,
除非他们可能决定我的生死
not when there's a chance my life could end up in their hands.
- 这是唯一原因？- 还有更好原因？
- Is that the only reason? - Can you think of a better one?
不知道 但我总希望你…
Me? No. But I was just hoping that you might,
除了公事公办 还有更私人的理由
thinking that somewhere, this got personal as well as physical!
我说我不要你去 你会高兴吗？
Would it make you feel any better if I didn't want you to do this?
- 当然会 - 那就高兴吧
- Yeah, much. - Then feel better!
我突然回到他身边…
You know, Sean will never be anything but suspicious…
一定会引起他的怀疑
if I pitch up saying, "Hey, honey, I'm home."
怎样才不引起他的怀疑？
What wouldn't make him suspicious?
除非我惹上大麻烦
That I needed him in some urgent way.
麻烦到束手无策
Destitute. In serious trouble.
自己根本没有办法解决
The kind I couldn't possibly sort out myself.
大麻烦…我总可以安排得来
Serious trouble, Nyah, is something that I can always arrange.
这微型发射器 绝不会露出马脚
This transponder chip is completely untraceable.
会把你的位置传送上卫星
It transmits your location to a satellite…
只有这部电脑才能够解读
which can be read by only this computer.
无论你去到哪里…
We can then track you to within three feet.
都可以追踪到
Anywhere.
我已经通知全世界的警方…
Since your arrest, I've been sending news bulletins…
我们逮捕了你
to every law enforcement agency.
我了解西恩…
I know Sean Ambrose,
坠机事件后他必定…
and I guarantee that after that airline crash,
他一定在密切留意每一个执法机构
he's monitoring everyone of them.
他知道你被捕了
He knows you're there.
就有办法把你弄出来
And he has the means to get you out.
娜雅
Nyah…
我不会放弃你
I'm not gonna lose you.
伊森·亨特？ 你好 我是威廉 叫我比利
Ethan Hunt? G'day, mate. I'm William Baird. Billy's okay.
无论想要什么 搬运或监视 找我准没错
Anything you need me to get, move or watch, just let me know.
我先到处看看
I'll have a look around.
- 狗屎 - 一点也没错
- Shit. - Yes, it is.
这不好笑
This ain't funny.
这是高级的古奇皮鞋
I just bought these $800 Gucci shoes,
你还叫我跟那小子同机
and you got me in a helicopter with this man?
连线 找到她了
Computer's up. We got her.
输入座标 展示画面
Let's put in the coordinates and get a visual.
怎么没有画面
Visuals aren't coming up.
人造卫星没我这么快
The satellite doesn't work as fast as I do.
路德 久仰大名了
Yeah, I heard about you, Luther. Just wanna say it's an honor…
很荣幸能跟你们两位合作
and a pleasure to be working with you blokes.
你不能快一点吗？
Come on. Isn't there any way we can speed this up?
没法 只有这部电脑才有这功能
With what? This is the only computer that'll do this.
伊森 来了
Ethan, here we go.
这样才算热情的欢迎
Now, there's a bloke who knows how to give a proper welcome.
不要误会 你也满热情的
Don't get me wrong, mate. You were very friendly also.
- 就是他？- 是
- Is it him? - It's him, Billy.
- 我们找到他了 - 状况还不明朗
- So we've got him! - We don't know what we've got.
我们不知道他抢走什么
'Cause we don't know what he's got,
或是他打算在悉尼干什么
where he's got it or what he's doing in Sydney with it.
- 没什么行李 - 我走得勿忙
- Not much luggage. - I left in a bit of a hurry.
我很感谢你 西恩
I'm incredibly grateful, Sean.
你怎找到我？
How in the world did you find me?
我用的是老方法
How I usually find you, Nyah.
凭魔术
Magic.
她身上没有追踪器
Mmm, mmm! No flies on her.
没有偷听器
No bugs, either. No transmissions.
她没可疑
She's clean.
女人总令人没有戒心
All cats are.
- 你的房间？- 嗯
- Your room? - Mmm.
- 我的房间？- 嗯
- And my room? - Hmm.
她进去了 在屋内
She did it. She's in the compound.
我们只是滚出一个雪球
Yeah? We just rolled up a snowball and tossed it into hell.
现在得看能得到什么
Now we'll see what chance it has.
穿上去
Try it on.
穿吧
Go ahead.
我不知道有没有记错你的尺码
I'm dying to see if I remembered your size.
你不想看我穿上它的样子吗？
You're not interested in seeing how it looks?
有兴趣
Oh, I am.
待会吧
Later.
每个英雄的诞生
Every search for a hero…
都有一个必备的条件
must begin with something that every hero requires…
一个坏蛋出现
a villain.
为了寻求我们的英雄伯洛尔芬
Therefore, in the search for our hero, Bellerophon,
我们制造了一头恶魔…奇美拉
we created a monster, Chimera.
诺考维奇是位分子生物学家
Nekhovich was a molecular biologist.
为什么大谈古代希腊神话？
Why is he going on about an old Greek myth?
他的专长是结合不同遗传基因
Nekhovich specialized in recombining DNA molecules.
在这个神话中
In the myth,
伯洛尔芬是屠杀了奇美拉的王子
Bellerophon was a prince who killed the Chimera.
奇美拉是个狮头蛇身…
A monster with the head of a lion and the tail of a serpent…
它让瘟疫降临人间
who plagued the ancient world.
我估计诺考维奇研制了一种叫 奇美拉的致命病毒…
I think Nekhovich created a monster virus named Chimera…
也研制了叫伯洛尔芬 的抗毒素
and the antivirus to kill it, named Bellerophon.
就是这么简单？
That simple, huh?
为什么不是？
Why not?
有人肯出三千七百万镑…
£37 million.
收购诺考维奇的发明
Now, that's a promising bid for Nekhovich's work.
不用担心 就快成功了
Don't look so worried, Hugh. We're halfway there.
我们把这数码磁碟…
We'll need this at the track…
带去马场 跟买家谈妥条件
if we're gonna get the other half.
那就…大功告成
Well, then…sorted.
未必
Not everything.
她来这里 究竟有什么目的？
Why do you think she's really here?
她的看法？抑或我的看法？
From her point of view or mine?
半年前她离开你…
Well, she wasn't exactly gagging for it…
不见得依依不舍
when she left you six months ago.
问题是 现在你能相信她吗？
The question is, do you trust her?
时机的确很敏感
One considers her timing, of course.
她在坠机后一个礼拜内被捕
Getting nicked within a week of the plane going down.
未免巧合 也有点可疑
Suggestive, even borderline suspicious,
但不能证明什么
but hardly conclusive.
反正你知道就好了
Well, you've thought about it, at any rate.
休斯 告诉我
Tell me, Hugh,
你在监视她的一举一动吗？
you don't exactly hang on Nyah's every word and gesture, do you?
你的指甲太长了
That's a fairly ratty nail that.
西恩 求求你！
Sean, please!
就算她是间谍 中情局派她来当卧底
Suppose she is some sort of Trojan horse sent in by IMF to spy on us.
送上门的肥肉为何不咬一口？
Why should I deny myself the pleasure of a ride or two?
你不认为我道行比她高？
Or don't you think I can learn more from her than she can from me?
能…
I do! I do! I do! I do!
休斯 你要明白…
Now, Hugh, you must realize that some of us…
有些人未必放得下一个色字
have the burden of sex to deal with.
我或者看不破她的来意…
And I may or may not know why she thinks she's here,
但我愿意冒这个险 因为…
but I'm willing to take the risk, because, Hugh,
我的确依依不舍
I am gagging for it.
加油！…
Come on!
亲爱的 你赢了！
Darling! You won!
- 大概是 - 为什么选中那匹老马？
- I suppose I did. - What made you pick that nag?
它一场都未赢过
He's never won a bloody thing.
- 它叫「午夜神偷」 - 原来如此
- "Thief in the Night." - Say no more.
我去买酒 你还爱喝百利尼斯？
I'm off to grab a drink. Do you still favor the Bellinis?
好
Mmm.
「天生虚荣」
"Naturally Vain."
什么？
Pardon me?
「天生虚荣」 第四场 赌它赢
Naturally Vain…in the fourth.
值得考虑 胜算甚高
Check her out. She's due.
（塞进耳内）
你可以当我在身边那样说话
You can speak as if I'm right by your side.
你在哪里？
Where are you?
跑道旁边 两点钟方向
Mounting enclosure just off the track, 2:00.
情况怎样？
How's it going?
一如既往
Just like old times.
一如既往？
Just like old times?
差不多
Just about.
你在安柏斯家看到谁？
Tell me who you've run into at Ambrose's.
以我的估计 那儿有五、六个人
Near as I can tell, there's about a half dozen other blokes about the place.
或者更多 其中一个休斯·史坦普 西恩的老朋友
Maybe more. Hugh Stamp, old friend of Sean's.
我只认得他 讨厌的傢伙
He's the only one I recognize. And a bit of a creep and then some.
他就在你左后方 正在望着你
We know him. He's over your left shoulder, looking at you right now.
安柏斯有一张报纸 上面有一堆钞票
Ambrose has photos of newspapers with money piled on them.
三千七百万英镑
Thirty seven million on the London Times.
怎么回事？
What's that about?
有人出价买奇美拉
Bids from possible Chimera buyers.
安柏斯跟一个人在酒吧
Ambrose is meeting some bloke in the bar.
大个子 淡黄色头发 他们在谈事情
Big bloke. Ginger hair. They're into something.
- 他是谁？- 我正在查
- Who is this guy? - Checking now, Ethan.
约翰·麦寇 拜塞制药厂总裁
John McCloy, CEO Biocyte Pharmaceuticals.
1989年并购拜塞药厂
In 1989, acquired Biocyte in a hostile takeover.
他是诺考维奇的老板
He was Nekhovich's boss.
没错 诺考维奇生前替他研制药物
Right. He worked for him as a research scientist at Biocyte.
安柏斯用数码相机给他看东西
Ambrose is showing something to McCloy on a digital camera.
不管那是什么 麦寇并不满意
Whatever McCloy's looking at, he's not happy about it.
安柏斯抽出…
Ambrose just pulled…
记忆卡塞进信封
the camera's memory card and put it into an envelope.
放到上衣左面内袋
Put it in his inner left jacket pocket.
重复：上衣左内袋
Confirm left jacket pocket.
收到
Roger that.
娜雅 安柏斯回来找你
Nyah. Nyah, Ambrose is on his way back to you.
- 有个信封…- 在他西装左边内袋
- There's an envelope inside…- His left jacket pocket.
对
That's right.
- 我怎样交给你？- 投注站第十二号
- Where do I meet you? - Betting table 12, off the paddock.
- 你应付得来吗？- 我会混过去
- Are you sure you're up to this? - I'll muddle through.
- 你回来了！- 你看好哪一匹？
- There you are! - See anything you like?
有 「天生虚荣」
Well, "Naturally Vain."
投注快要截止 我却没有钱
But they're about to close the betting, and I haven't a bean.
- 娜雅！- 介意吗？
- Nyah! - Would you mind terribly?
绝不介意 但你要还
Not at all. But, um, you are gonna pay for it.
- 连本带利 - 当然
- And with interest. - I have no doubt.
等一等
Hold on.
替我落一千块注
Put down a thousand for me.
- 买赢的？- 那还用说
- To win? - What else?
- 比利 别让他跟着娜雅 - 包在我身上好了
- Billy, make sure Nyah's not followed. - No worries, mate.
路德 准备数码相机传送
Luther, digital camera ready to transmit.
拿到十二号赌桌
Betting table 12.
- 请进 - 谢谢
- There you go. - Fine.
真是对不起 老兄
Oh, sorry about that, mate.
你说什么？
Say again?
你最好给我小心点
Whatever you're about, in future, watch your step.
你不会知道会碰上什么人
Never know who you might run into.
洗手间呢？
So where's the loo?
谢谢你
Thanks, mate.
你好吗？
How'd you do?
不要转身
Don't turn around.
还可以
I managed.
你转过来了
You turned around.
转又怎样？打我屁股？
What are you gonna do? Spank me?
伊森 随时可以接收
I'm booted up. Go, Ethan.
接收到没有？
Are you getting this?
（奇美拉感染血液）
瑟盖·葛斯基
Sergei Gradski
感染20小时后
20 hours after exposure.
（感染27小时后）
（感染31小时后）
（细胞迅速摧毁）
（葛斯基博士 于34小时后死亡）
真可怕
God.
史坦普从厕所出来了
Stamp 's out of the loo.
他向你们那儿走去
He's coming out of the tunnel, heading your way, mate.
- 我要你离开安柏斯家 - 你说什么？
- I want you out of Ambrose's place. - What are you talking about?
怎么了？你看到什么？
What's happened? What did you see?
伊森 他向你背后走过来
Okay, he's coming up behind you, Ethan.
你已完成任务 我要你离开澳洲
You've done your job. I want you out of Australia.
- 距离三十步 - 我该怎么离开？
- Thirty steps. - How do you suggest I go about it?
20 19
Twenty, nineteen
难道你舍不得离开他？
He's touched your heart. You need to think it over.
15 14 12 11…
Fifteen, fourteen, twelve, eleven.
尽快离开 把耳机给我
I want you out of there now. Give me the earpiece.
- 九 八 - 你不走
- Nine, Ethan. Eight. - If you don't get out of there,
我就去救你
I'm coming in and getting you out.
伊森 快走
Ethan, get out of there!
下了注没有？
You placed your bet, ma'am?
刚刚下了
Just.
准备好了
Horses are ready to race.
开始
They're off!
你的马在外跑道迎头而上
Come on! Come on! Your nag's making a run for it on the outside!
加油！
Come on! Come on!
你又赢了！
You picked another winner!
还以为你要去吃晚餐
I thought you were going to dinner.
收藏好诺考维奇的记忆卡
Hugh, take care of the Nekhovich memory card.
在哪里？
Where is it?
在我的西装口袋
In the envelope in my jacket pocket.
右边的口袋
My right jacket pocket.
拜塞制药厂采用先进太阳能设计
We at our state-of-the-art solar-powered Biocyte building,
我们的宗旨是预防胜于治疗
recognize that eternal vigilance is the price of health,
我们资助皇家爱德华王子医院
whether it's funding the teaching center at the Royal Prince Edward Hospital,
主张废除使用气溶胶
removing aerosol products from the market…
为第三世界注射防疫针
or braving the influenza quarantine at Bruny Island late last month.
我们拜塞制药厂 为你的一生…奉献出一生
At Biocyte, your life is our life's work.
这是大好的机会
We've got an opportunity here.
我决不会错过
I'm not going to miss it.
乔治 载我回家去
George, take me home.
乔治？
George?
George!
（药厂老板 死于罕见感冒病毒）
怎么搞的
What the hell?
西恩…
Sean?
别紧张
Easy.
伊森
Oh, Ethan.
没事吧？
Are you okay?
现在没事了
Yeah, I am now.
- 怎么回事？- 一个老朋友来看你
- What is this? - A visit from an old friend.
你不是撞机死了吗？
You crashed on the plane. You're dead.
死 免不了 只是时间问题
Dead, certainly. But dead is a little extreme.
当我的同事…葛斯基的脉搏 血压…
On the other hand, when my colleague Gradski had your pulse…
跟你一样的时候 他已经活不过一天
and your blood pressure, he had less than a day to live.
你感染了奇美拉病毒
You are infected with Chimera, my friend.
不用叫人来
No use, my friend.
护士不想淌这浑水
The medical staff wants no part of this.
医生也不想白白送死
Doctors don't fancy the idea of dying any more than anybody else.
我怎么会被感染？
How could I possibly be infected?
葛斯基死前27小时…也这样问
That's exactly what Gradski said 27 hours before he died.
你有解药 王八蛋
You've got the antidote, you miserable bastard!
- 你把抗毒素全都偷走了 - 我…
- You stole Bellerophon! All of it! - My…
你这个我需要它 你这个俄罗斯疯子！
I need it! I need it now, you whacked-out Russian Gypsy!
葛斯基呢？ 你为什么故意让他感染病毒？
And what about Gradski, who you deliberately infected with Chimera?
我怎么知道二十小时内要替他解毒
How was I to know they needed to be treated with Bellerophon within 20 hours?
- 你可以问我 - 你还是不懂 是吧？
- By asking me. - You still don't get it, do you?
我需要知道病毒真正的威力
I needed to know just how bad the disease was in the real world,
不只是实验结果
not just the lab.
你混合了几种病毒基因…
You were genetically splicing together strains of influenza…
研制出一种抗毒素
to create a cure for all influenzas.
但你也研制出致命病毒奇美拉
But you were also creating a disease so terrible in Chimera,
抗毒素就变成无价之宝
the cure would be priceless.
我需要奇美拉来促销伯洛尔芬
I needed Chimera in order to peddle Bellerophon.
这并不难明白吧？
It's not that difficult to understand, is it?
我有病毒 你有抗毒素
Look, I've got the virus. You've got the cure.
我两样都需要
I need them both.
以前盘尼西林能解百毒
Time was a shot of penicillin would knock off…
现在不管用了
every bloody bug in the zoo. Not anymore.
现在得了感冒都用不着吃药
If I couldn't make money killing the microscopic little shits out there,
你得帮我散播可以赚钱的病毒
well, you'd help me put one out there that I could make money on.
这就是前因后果
Well, there it is. I've confessed.
我约翰·麦寇
I, John C. McCloy,
就是为了赚钱
am in business to make money.
不管你跟安柏斯是怎么谈的
Now, forget any deal you may have made with that thug Ambrose.
我要你把我治好 继续工作
Get me treated, and let's go back to work.
你还不知道…
You know,
现在已经太迟了
I think it's a little late for that.
你见到葛斯基…
Do give my regards to Gradski…
替我问候他
if you see him.
好了…
Well…
我已经听到…
I've heard…
我该知道的事
all I need to hear.
最重要的是我们不要惊动西恩
it's imperative that we do nothing to alarm Ambrose.
什么？
What?
你叫我立刻下来
You told me to get out of there as soon as possible.
- 我以为你是来救我的 - 嘘 嘘…
- I thought you were here to collect me! - Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh!
听我说 现在没有时间解释
Listen to me. There's no time to talk.
最重要的是…绝对最重要的是…
It is critical, absolutely critical,
照安柏斯的话去做
that you do whatever Ambrose asks.
明不明白？
Do you understand me?
别担心
Don't worry.
这件事…很快会结束
It will all be over…very soon.
我可以保证
That's a promise.
走吧 回去吧
Go on. Off you go.
路德 我们知道这么多
Luther, we know this much. Nekhovich gets on a plane…
诺考维奇搭飞机 去亚特兰大的疾病控制中心
to go to the Center for Disease Control in Atlanta.
他带了自己研制的奇美拉病毒
He's carrying a virus he created, Chimera,
以及抗毒素 伯洛尔芬
and the cure for that virus, Bellerophon.
安柏斯没有病毒
Ambrose doesn't have the virus.
所以他需要麦寇
That's why Ambrose needs McCloy.
我们如果潜入药厂消灭病毒
So we go into Biocyte, kill Chimera,
安柏斯的抗毒素没有用处
Ambrose has a cure without a disease,
我们就成功了
and we're home free.
不出你所料 伊森今晚绑走麦寇
You were right. Hunt stung McCloy tonight.
他知道了 他一定会到拜塞制药厂
So he knows. He'll be going into Biocyte.
好 那么 我们掌握到他的行踪了
Good. Then we'll know where he'll be, don't we?
干得好 休斯
Well done, Hugh.
干得好
Well done.
你到家了 到家了
Oi! You're home, mate. Home.
乔治呢？
Where's George?
我平时的司机乔治呢？
My regular driver? Where is he?
他得了感冒 回家休息了
He's gone home sick. Touch of the flu.
- 这就是拜塞制药厂？- 嗯
- Is the building up and running yet? - Mmm.
- 不是吧？- 不好意思 这里就是
- That's not exactly it. - Sorry, but this is a Biocyte facility.
这是他们的仓库 马上就好
Their storage structure. I'll have it up in a minute.
- 你看看 - 从内部开始
- Okay, take a look at this. - Start from the inside out.
奇美拉病毒都存在这里
All storage and production of Chimera is done here,
42楼的实验室内
in this lab on the 42nd floor.
伊森的目标是
Hunt's target will be the Chimera,
放在42楼的病毒
stored and manufactured at Biocyte on the 42nd floor.
他的一贯行动习惯是…
If you look at Hunt's operational history, and I have,
避免正面冲突
he invariably favors misdirection over confrontation.
他绝对不会从守卫最森严的一楼着手
He'll never break into Biocyte from the bottom where security is heaviest.
停车场没入口
No garage entrances.
大厅有五名警卫巡逻
Lobby's protected by five guards on rotating patrol.
我不从地面进去 从屋顶怎么样？
Not goin' in from the ground. Show me the atrium.
屋顶？独一无二
The atrium? One of a kind.
从大楼中央一路到底
Runs down through the center of the building.
24小时天然照明 采用折射镜和太阳能电池
Provides 24-hournaturallight via mirrors and daylight storage cells.
为病毒提供最适度的培植环境
Optimal growing conditions for the virus.
底部的玻璃地板下面是实验室
Ends in a glass floor which doubles as part of the lab ceiling.
日落后屋顶就关闭
Uh-uh. The atrium roof closes at sundown.
假如活叶板在晚上开启超过四十秒
And if the louvers are up for more than 40seconds at night,
会触动警铃
the civil emergency alarms are tripped.
连我都无法解除
Those, even I can't stop.
伊森 我们一共有四十秒
Ethan, we have a total of 40 seconds…
让你进去然后收回缆绳
to get you in and the cables out.
伊森多数会会从屋顶进去
No, Hunt will prefer to enter Biocyte somewhere from the top…
因为楼顶保安最松
where security is minimal.
他一定会亲自大玩特技动作…
He'll undoubtedly engage in some aerobatic insanity…
却不肯动警卫一根头发
before he'll risk harming a hair on a security guard's head.
- 试音 听到吗？- 听到
- Check check. Got copy? - You're five-by-five.
路德 情况怎样？
Luther, how we doin '?
还不行 我会通知你
Not there yet, Ethan. I'll give you the word.
比利 准备好没有？
Billy, ready to go?
五秒后行动
Okay, package away in five…
我还没好 活叶板还未打开
I'm not ready. The louvers aren't moving.
快点 路德 要行动了
Come on, Luther! We gotta go!
我在输入密码
Wait, there's a glitch in the access code.
路德 时间无多 开始倒数
Luther, we're out of time. On the count.
开吧 乖乖打开
Please, baby, open up, open up.
- 五 四… - 快点
- Five, four… - Come on!
三 二 一！
three, two, one!
- 我下去了！- 等一等！
- I'm going now! - Ethan, wait!
25 24 23…
Twenty five, twenty four, twenty three…
22 21 20…
Twenty two, twenty one, twenty.
19秒后要把缆绳收回去
Ethan, you've got 19seconds to clear the cable.
收回缆绳！
Okay, retracting cable!
九 八 七 六 五…
Nine, eight, seven, six,
五 四 三 二…
five, four, three, two…
缆绳收回！
Cable's clear!
开启追踪器 追踪货物位置 收回了缆绳
Transponder activated. Reading package and cable clear.
他会在千均一发之间…
He'll breach the lab at the only possible time,
进入实验室
whether you break in from the ground or the roof.
二十三时零一分
It's 2300 hours, one minute…
空气过滤器发动机开动 会掩盖伊森在里面的声音
when the air filtration generators will cover the sound of Hunt's break-in…
同时 趁警卫换班…
and the rotating guards make the building vulnerable…
我们从楼下进入
to our break-in from below.
伊森 发动机就快启动了
Ethan, the generator's about to go active.
开动后 我们会中断联络八分钟
Just a friendly reminder. We'll be out of contact for eight minutes.
我肯定伊森会把病毒…
I'm betting Hunt will destroy Chimera…
全部毁灭
rather than attempt to preserve any part of it.
病毒放在两个地方
He'll have to do it in two places.
一部分…保温室里的病毒培养瓶
First, the incubation room where the growth vials are kept.
另一部分存放在…
And finally, in the inoculation chamber…
疫苗接种室 三支装有病毒的注射枪
holding the last remaining Chimera virus in three injection guns.
要阻止他消灭注射枪内的病毒
He won't be allowed to destroy the virus in those guns.
怎么了？你们第一次准时
What's this? You're on time, for once?
不见得 老兄
Not exactly, sport.
约翰·麦寇
John C. McCloy.
比利 我们有麻烦
Billy, I think we've got a problem.
娜雅来这儿了 你听到吗？
Nyah's on the wing up early. Billy, do you copy?
听到 路德 娜雅在哪里？
Yeah, I got you, Luther. Sorry, exactly where is she?
- 在大楼里 - 什么？
- In the building. - Say again, mate.
你说她在大楼里？
Sounds like you're saying she's in the building.
是的 她在药厂里
I am. She is.
不是只有她一个人 对吧？
Uh, well, then she's not likely to be alone, is she, mate?
她进了电梯往伊森那儿去
She's in the elevator, headed towards Ethan.
问题是 总共有多少人？
The question is: How many of them?
等发电机停了才能警告伊森
I can't get through to Ethan, not till the generators go.
- 什么时候停？ - 五分三十秒后
- Yeah, well, when's that? - Not for another five-and-a-half minutes.
病毒酸碱值 温度…
Chimera in vitro pH and temperature level…
超出最适当范围
outside optimal range.
病毒酸碱值 温度…
Chimera in vitro pH and temperature level…
超出最适当范围
outside optimal range.
奇美拉病毒受到威胁
Chimera working seed stock pH at critical level.
警告：病毒受到威胁
Alert. Chimera stock life threatened.
警告：病毒被消灭
Alert. Chimera stock life terminated.
（病毒已经消灭）
伊森…快点吧
Come on, Ethan. Come on.
物体并无污染
Subject is contaminant-free.
污染程度：零
Zero contaminant factor.
快点 快点…
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
路德 有什么办法？
Luther, what the hell can we do?
有什么办法？
What can we do?
唯有希望黄点到达红点前 他已消灭病毒
Hope he kills all the bugs before the yellow dot gets to the red one.
无论如何…
However we travel,
出发后二十小时内 必须抵达目的地
I must arrive at my destination within 20 hours of departure.
我怎么知道二十小时内…
How was I to know that he needed to be treated…
要替他解毒？
with Bellerophon within 20hours?
抓住他
Get him.
还等多久才可以连络上？
How much longer before you can reach him?
还有29秒 发动机关闭才可以
We've got 29 seconds before the generators turn off,
然后伊森能够连上
then Ethan will be back on-line.
路德！…
Luther! Luther!
不要开枪！
Hold your fire!
Hold your fire, damn it!
伊森
Well, Hunt…
近况如何？
how've you been?
患了点感冒
Fighting a bit of a cold.
假扮你最难的地方是
You know, that was the hardest part of having to portray you…
每十五分钟 就像白痴一样傻笑
grinning like an idiot every 15 minutes.
假扮你最难的是…
I would've thought the hardest part was curbing that pressing need of yours…
动不动就杀人
to get your gun off.
你急着毁掉那架747客机
You were in such a hurry to knock off that 747…
连奇美拉是什么还没知道
you never figured out where Chimera really was.
- 我知道奇美拉是什么 - 哦
- I knew where it was. - Oh.
诺考维奇把病毒注射入自己体内…
Then you knew the only way Nekhovich could smuggle the live virus…
才可以利用自己的血液 把病毒带走
is by injecting himself and using his own bloodstream as a petri dish.
你也知道…你杀掉他
You knew that…while you were knocking him off,
也杀掉你所要的病毒
destroying the very thing you came for.
不要开枪！停手！
Stop! Put a sock in it!
打中注射枪 病毒就会散播出来
Hit that bloody gun, and you'll spray the virus all over the place!
各位 病毒在这里
There it is, guys.
最后一支
The last of it.
价高者得
What was the top bid?
你愿意出更高价？
Why? You gonna make me a better offer?
高过三千七百万镑？不会
Than £37 million? Not really.
有人在向你告密
Somebody has been slipping you our mail.
出来吧 坏女孩
Come on out here, you bad girl.
西恩 这件事与她无关 放她走吧
Sean, she doesn't belong here. Let her go.
伊森 不是因为你…
She wouldn't be here…
她也不会在这里出现
if it wasn't for you, Hunt.
由现在起…她是生是死 看你了
From this moment, you are responsible for what happens to her.
假如你爱护她…
And if you're looking out for her well-being,
最好叫她捡起注射枪…交来给我
I suggest you advise her to pick up the injection gun and bring it to me.
看你了 伊森
Ball's in your court, Hunt.
娜雅在药厂内 听到吗？
Nyah's in the building. Do you copy?
谢谢
Thank you.
你怎么知道他得到之后不会杀你？
How do you know he won't shoot you the minute he's got it?
拜托 你得让她自己决定
Please. One can't hold Nyah responsible for her actions.
你也了解女人 女人是最善变了
You know women, mate. Like monkeys they are.
抓住下一根树枝才会放手
Won't let go of one branch till they get a grip on the next!
娜雅 捡起来 我掩护你
Get it, Nyah. I'll cover you.
我在等着
I am waiting.
事情跟你原来想的不一样
Things haven't exactly worked out the way you thought they would, Ethan.
抱歉
Sorry.
臭婊子！
You bitch!
你不能杀我 西恩 我这婊子
You're not gonna shoot me, Sean. Not this bitch.
因为贱人值三千七百万镑
'Cause she's worth £37 million.
- 你打算怎样？- 我没有打算
- What did you think you were doing? - I wasn't thinking!
我只是不想让你受伤
Just trying to stop you from getting hurt, that's all!
你说自己没有正义感
You who don't have a conscience.
我大概说了谎
I guess I lied.
你救不了我们两个 对不对？
You can't get us both out of here, can you?
我感染了病毒
I'm infected with Chimera.
你没有选择余地 开枪吧
You know you don't have a choice. Just do it.
立刻开枪！
Do it now!
19小时58分钟之内…
We've got 19 hours and 58 minutes!
我会替你注射抗毒素
I'll get Bellerophon into your system before then!
活下去 我不会失去你
Just stay alive! I'm not going to lose you!
想不想跪地求饶？
Feel like pleading for your life?
那就死了好了…
Well, then, how about dying…
你死了 我发大财
so you can make me a lot of money?
几个钟头后 你会一举成名…
In just a few hours time, you can be assured…
成为新病毒之母
of going down in history as the Typhoid Mary of Oz.
祝你好运
G'day.
和卫星连上线才能找到娜雅
There's not a chance of locating Nyah until can access the satellite.
想接收卫星资料需要修妥电脑 这得花点时间
And there's not a chance of doing that until I can get this computer fixed.
她有多少时间？
How much time does she have left?
不多 不管怎样 她自有决定
Not long. But whatever happens, Nyah will take care of Nyah.
- 什么意思？ - 若没有抗毒素…
- What do you mean? - Unless we dose her with Bellerophon,
娜雅会自杀
Nyah will kill herself.
所以事不宜迟
So first things first.
安柏斯一伙人到了…
Ethan, Ambrose and his team have arrived…
不见娜雅
over the bridge, and Nyah's not with him, mate.
收到了
Copy that.
你行不行？看来警卫挺多的
You all right, mate? Looks like pretty heavy security from here.
你认为怎样？
What's it look like from there?
很危险
Risky.
西蒙？西蒙！
Simon? Simon!
不要走开
Stay here.
从左前方入了屋
Breached the structure at the 10:00 grating.
DNA吻合 血液充满奇美拉病毒
It's a DNA match. The blood's loaded with Chimera.
他们的确有伯洛尔芬 抗毒素
And they certainly have Bellerophon.
你既然有病毒及抗毒素…
Well, then you've got both the virus and the antivirus,
我现在可以给你三千万
which means I've got 30 million for you.
我们要的不仅是钞票
Not exactly. We don't want just your cash.
- 还要什么？- 股份 麦寇先生
- What do you want? - Stock, Mr. McCloy.
准确而言 现值三千万的股份
Stock options, to be a little more precise.
在市中心释放她
Cut her loose…right in the center of town.
人口越多越好
The more crowded the better.
伊森 刚截到安柏斯的通讯 他们释放了娜雅
Ethan, just picked up an Ambrose call. Nyah's been dropped off.
- 她在哪里？- 悉尼某处
- Where is she? - Somewhere in Sydney.
悉尼某处？能够准确些吗？
Somewhere in Sydney? Care to harden the target?
不能够…
I can't until…
电脑还未接通卫星
I can get the GPS up on our computer. It's down.
时间不多了
The clock is ticking.
生产抗毒素要多久？
How quickly can you manufacture more of the antivirus?
一有样板 立即可以生产
No time at all, once I've got it.
不出几星期 拜塞股价很快就会涨停板
Good. Biocyte stock is just a few weeks away from going through the roof.
- 为什么？- 奇美拉病毒爆发
- What are you talking about? - An outbreak of Chimera.
- 在哪里爆发？- 由悉尼市开始 向全球蔓延
- Where? - Downtown Sydney, for a start.
你制造解药
You create the supply, Mr. McCloy.
我们制造需求
We've just created the demand.
悉尼三百万人…
Three million people in Sydney…
澳洲一千七百万人…
and 17 million people in Australia…
几天内 个个都要抗毒素
are going to need Bellerophon within the next few days,
迟早全世界人人都要
not to mention the rest of the world.
我的条件是这样
Now, this is how it's going to work.
- 总共有多少股份？ - 9340万
- Wallis, the shares outstanding are? - 93.4 million.
即是说我们要买下48万张选择股
Which means, Mr. McCloy, we need to get our hands on 480, 000 options.
我要借用你的三千万
We'll borrow your 30 million to buy those options.
你的股票每股最多31元
Your stock has never sold above $31 a share.
当它涨到二百元
When your stock goes north of 200,
一定会的 我的股票就会值几十亿元
which it will, those options will be worth billions,
到时候我就有拜塞制51%股权
and I will own 51% of Biocyte.
太荒谬了
This is outrageous.
我不会让你控制我的公司
I will not let you take control of my company.
坐下
Sit down.
你想做亿万富豪抑或想破产？
You'll be a billionaire. It's better than being broke.
很多恐怖分子和制药厂都等着要货
I have terrorists and other pharmaceutical companies standing in line.
接不接纳我的条件随便你 麦寇先生
The ball's in your court, Mr. McCloy.
去把那个兔崽子宰了
Run that bastard down.
没时间了 麦寇先生
We're running short on time, Mr. McCloy.
我们的交易还没完成
We have got to conclude our business.
好吧 开始转帐
Yes. Start the transfer.
钱到手 通知我
Follow it…and let me know.
（转帐中）
慢慢举起手来
Raise your hands very slowly.
你真要我举手？
Sure you want me to do this?
慢慢把手举起来
Raise your hands very slowly.
伊森 你听到吗？
Ethan, Ethan, do you copy? Do you copy?
继续转帐
Keep it going!
（转帐中）
西恩 我逮到那只兔崽子了
Sean, this rat's reached the end of the maze.
死了没有？
Is he alive?
半死不活
Yeah, more or less.
把他带来
Bring him to me.
起飞
Go!
（转帐完成）
西恩 钱到手了
Sean, transfer completed.
干得好 史坦普
Well done, Stamp. Well done.
快说话
Stop mumbling!
我恐怕他说不了了
I'm afraid he's got no choice.
因为我把他下巴打歪了
I believe I broke his jaw.
史坦普 有你的
Stamp, I'm impressed.
咱们时间不多 亨特
Right. We don't have a lot of time, Hunt.
有什么话 快说
What ever you got to say, say it now.
露一露招牌笑容 怎样？
How about giving us a big smile?
- 不笑？- 你在干什么？
- No? - What are you doing?
跪下来
Get down on your knees.
给你见识见识…
Now, this is what's known…
这才叫大开杀戒
as getting your gun off.
他在那里！
There he is!
伊森！
Ethan!
躲开 找她去
Just back off and pinpoint your positions!
路德 解决桥上的人
Luther, clear the bridge for me!
亨特往桥那儿冲过去了
Hunt's heading for the bridge, coming in at 12:00 high.
我火大了
Oh, I'm mad now.
- 你没事吧？ - 臭小子射穿我的范思哲！
- You all right, mate? - That punk put a hole in my Versace!
伊森 电脑接通 找到娜雅
Ethan, the computer's up. I've got Nyah.
她离开市中心
She's moved out of the city.
她正走向北边的悬崖
She's on the north head bluff approaching the cliffs.
- 我还未接收到画面 - 收到了！
- But I can't get a visual. - Copy!
她的时间不多了
She's only got a little time left!
赶快去接她
Track ahead and pick her up!
- 我不能够瞄准！- 伊森 我们没法掩护你
- I can't get a good shot. - Ethan, we won't be able to cover you!
耳机坏了 用卫星定位系统
My earpiece is failing! You've got me on GPS!
把她带来找我
Bring her to me!
比利 北边的悬崖 快去
Billy, north head bluff. Haul ass.
- 冲过去 继续开枪 - 我看不见
- Get out there and keep firing! - I can't see anything!
开慢点…
Slow down, mate! Slow down!
还有两公里
Range is 2K.
来吧 用刀杀我 这种死法不错
Go ahead. Use it, Hunt. It's not a bad way to go.
总比那臭婊子的死法好
It's a lot better than the way that bitch is gonna die.
她在那儿
Hey, there she is!
你应该杀了我
You should've killed me.
娜雅的血液内似乎…
Miss Hall's blood, it appears,
一点奇美拉病毒都没有
has absolutely no elements of the Chimera virus,
连抗毒素都没有
not even antibodies.
我猜也是
Yes. I gathered as much.
亨特 我给你的任务是…
But you were under specific instructions, Mr. Hunt,
把病毒的活样本带回来
to bring back a living sample of the Chimera virus.
我想知道重新拿回病毒后…
I'd be very interested to know how, after you managed this recovery,
怎么会被销毁？
it subsequently got destroyed.
被火烧掉 最好的方法
By fire. It's the best way, really.
哦 好吧 亨特
Oh. Well, Mr. Hunt,
这次任务霍小姐作用不小
as for Miss Hall, in light of her efforts,
她的犯罪记录当然会
her criminal record will certainly be expunged.
一笔勾销 我猜你应该同意
Wiped out. I'm assuming you approve.
是的
I do.
顺便问句 她现在在哪里？
Yeah. Where is she now, by the way? Any idea?
我也不大清楚
I don't know. Not exactly.
你有什么打算？
So, what are your plans?
不知道 或者度假去
I don't know. Uh, some sort of vacation.
我会告诉你我去哪里度假
I'll let you know where I'm going.
你不一定要告诉我
You don't have to do that.
说了就不算度假
It wouldn't be a vacation if you did.
咱们去度假吧
Let's get lost.